Hello friends, welcome
back to our YouTube channel. As you
can see, today we are talking about the ICC Bank Recruitment
bike.
Friends, there are vacancies for eight and a half posts.
In this, some things like education
news items, are the selection will be through entry
medium. In this, for
50,000, I have 12th and 12th edition
pass, all of them can update. It is an all India
job. Both male and female can apply. Let's
talk about
ICICI Bank Recruitment for 21,
application can be done online through other posts
and if the bank has notified for the post,
ICC Bank job
opening APN is Rishi, the latest
notification for the recruitment for various
posts in ICC Bank Career PIO
Manager Officer, if
friends can also apply for the post, you can
see that the last date is 31st December, please do
more on this candid camera that where to get
pass is necessary. There is a
limit in this, friends, minimum 18 and  There is
no maximum flaw, friends, there is an
ad election given in it to loot by doing ads etc.,
you can see this, the starting date
of action in it will be friends, twice a week on
21st and the last date in it will be friends 31st
December 21, there will be no
time for anything in it for General, OBC, SC, ST and for that
you have to go and check in the office notice,
friends, a very good salary has been given in it, the
salary for candidates was
50,000, friends, I have
told in the series,
how to apply for half milk, you have to
open the official website of such bank,
you have to register in it online and
apply in it, friends, the candidate will also be
selected and the interview process, friends,
in this the candidate will be selected through the interview process, this is the only way the
candidate will be selected, as you can
see, full motivation for Axis
Bank Branch Manager, Probation Officer, Customer
Service, Human Resource Manager, Branch
Manager, friends, in this friends, very good gifts have been given,
as you can see, you have to
apply online only through online medium,
friends  If you like this video,
please like it and subscribe to the channel.
Thank you so much for this.